A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller, Vice Presidential records, National Commission on Water Quality, Series 9 FA379
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Construction Grants - FY '72 Funds and Slowdown of Programs, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 944)
- Construction Grants - Status March 31 and June 30, 1972 - Questionnaire to States (Box 28, Folder 945)
- Construction Grants - Status (State Worksheets and Letters) Questionnaire to States (Box 28, Folder 946)
- Construction Grants - Status June 30, 1972 Responses from States (Questionnaire) (Box 28, Folder 947)
- Construction Grants - EPA Status Reports, April 30, 1972 - November 30, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 948)
- Construction Grants - Reallocation FY '72 Funds (Law Enacted Extending Date to May 15, 1973), 1972-1973 (Box 28, Folder 949)
- Construction Grants - FY '72 Authorization for $350 Million in PL92-500, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 950)
- Construction Grants - Requirements for Approval Under PL92-500, December 1972 (Box 28, Folder 951)
- Construction Grants - Impoundment of Funds (Box 28, Folder 952)
- Construction Grants - Allocations from $18 Billion, FY '73, 74, 75 and 76, 1973-1976 (Box 28, Folder 953)
- Construction Grants - Phased Funding (Delaware Plan) (Box 28, Folder 954)
  See Regulations
- Construction Grants - Regulation Draft December 28, 1972; Interim February 10 and February 28, 1973, 1972-1973 (Box 28, Folder 955)
- Construction Grants - Regulation Drafts, November, December, and January; Final, December 1974 (with Amendments) (Box 28, Folder 956)
- Construction Grants - Advance Funding - New York Plan, March 1973 (Box 28, Folder 957)
- Construction Grants - Meeting of States (Ad Hoc Task Force), March 15, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 958)
- Construction Grants - EPA Policies and Sansom Reports (NUCA), 1973-1976 (Box 28, Folder 959)
- Construction Grants - Tables (Obligations, Outlays, etc.) FY '75-76, 1975-1976 (Box 28, Folder 960)
- Construction Grants - PL92-500 - Obligations Prior to March 2, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 961)
- Construction Grants - EPA Status Report, February 28, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 962)
- Construction Grants - Obligations FY '73 and '74 Under PL92-500 (Box 28, Folder 963)
- Construction Grants - EPA Recommendation to OMB (Office of Management and Budget), mid-1975 (Box 28, Folder 964)
- Construction Grants - Sub-Agreements - EPA Regulations, 1974-1976 (Box 28, Folder 965)
- Construction Grants - Cost Effectiveness (Sec. 212 of PL92-500) (Box 28, Folder 966)
- Construction Grants - Cost Escalation - EPA Policy, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 967)
- Construction Grants - Costs to Industry (11 Major Industries), CEQ Study, March 1972 (Box 28, Folder 968)
- Construction Grants - Costs: New York State Figures Used by NAR at December 9, 1971 House Hearings (Box 28, Folder 969)
- Construction Grants - Costs to Industry (Wall Street Journal Survey), November 1971 (Box 28, Folder 970)
- Construction Grants - Bureau of Census Report, November 1976 (Box 28, Folder 971)
- Construction Grants - EPA Report, "Economics of Clean Water", 1973 (Box 28, Folder 972)
- Construction Grants - Costs of Clean Water and Jobs Created, 1973-1975 (Box 28, Folder 973)
- Construction Grants - Costs/Needs Survey (To Be Completed February 1977) (Box 28, Folder 974)
- Construction Grants - Needs Survey (Municipals) for FY '75 Allocations for Construction Grants, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 975)
- Construction Grants - Costs/Needs Survey (Municipals) "Cost of Clean Water", May 1972 (Box 28, Folder 976)
- Construction Grants - Needs Survey (Municipals) for FY '76 Allocations for Construction Grants, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 977)
- Construction Grants - States' Efforts - Tables Showing Progress FY '73-75, 1973-1975 (Box 28, Folder 978)
- New York State Program - Environment (Overall) (Box 29, Folder 979)
- New York State Program - STP Projects June 1971-Pending EPA Approval, January 1972; 45 Projects Withdrawn, 1971-1972 (Box 29, Folder 980)
- New York State Program - Briefing of Congressional Delegation, January 27, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 981)
- New York State Program - Diamond Position Paper - Letter to Congressional Delegation, February 8, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 982)
- New York State Program - Niagara Falls, January-May 1972 (Box 29, Folder 983)
- New York State Program - North River Plant - Manhattan, New York City, 1971-1976 (Box 29, Folder 984)
- New York State Program - Priority List of Projects Pending, March-May 1972 (Box 29, Folder 985)
- New York State Program - Bond Issue (Environment), 1972 (Box 29, Folder 986)
- New York State Program - Henry Diamond (Miscellaneous), 1972-1973 (Box 29, Folder 987)
- New York State Program - Allocations, 1957-1972 (Box 29, Folder 988)
- New York State Program - Overall (Water Pollution), 1973-1976 (Box 29, Folder 989)
- New York State Program - Priority System, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 990)
- New York State Program - Priority List, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 991)
- New York State Program - Priority List, FY '77, August 16, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 992)
- New York State Program - New York City Tour by NCWQ Staff (Box 29, Folder 993)
- New York State Program - Permit Program (Box 29, Folder 994)
- New York State Program - DEC Annual Report "Pure Waters" (Box 29, Folder 995)
- New York State Program - FY '76 Program for Water Pollution, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 996)
- New York State Program - PCB Controversy, 1975-1976 (Box 29, Folder 997)
- New York State Program - Sludge Disposal and Ocean Dumping (Box 29, Folder 998)
- New York State Program - Lake Champlain (Box 29, Folder 999)
- New York State Program - Tocks Island (Box 29, Folder 1000)
- Pre-Financing - Statistics (All States) (Box 29, Folder 1001)
- Pre-Financing - Dispute Over Reimbursement Eligibility Under PL660 (Box 29, Folder 1002)
- Pre-Financing - Accuracy of EPA Statistics, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 1003)
- Pre-Financing - Data on New York City (Box 29, Folder 1004)
- Reimbursements - $200 Million from FY '71 Appropriations, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 1005)
- Reimbursements - New York State (Earned Reimbursables), December 1971 (Box 29, Folder 1006)
- Reimbursements - Retroactive Grants, 1971-1972 (Box 29, Folder 1007)
- Reimbursements - Definition of "Construction" (Box 29, Folder 1008)
- Reimbursements - States to House Appropriations, Requesting Funds (Box 29, Folder 1009)
- Reimbursements - New York State Policies / Actions to Recover Pre-Financing Obligations (Box 29, Folder 1010)
- Reimbursements - Status Mid-1976 (1973 Act to Amend Authorization) (Box 29, Folder 1011)
- Reimbursements - Aquaculture Projects (EPA Regulations) (Box 29, Folder 1012)
- Reimbursements - Air Pollution Act - Constitutionality (Box 29, Folder 1013)
- Reimbursements - Air Pollution - National Air Quality Commission (Box 29, Folder 1014)
- Reimbursements - American Society of Civil Engineers, 1973-1974 (Box 29, Folder 1015)
- Reimbursements - Wastewater Effluent Limits (Box 29, Folder 1016)
- Reimbursements - Best Practicable Waste Treatment Technology (BPWWT) for Municipalities - EPA Regulations (Box 29, Folder 1017)
- Reimbursements - Decentralization - Task Force Report to EPA, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 1018)
- Reimbursements - Cost-Benefit Analysis and Water Pollution Policy - Symposium: EPA and Urban Institute (sec. 104 (6) of PL92-500), September 1973 (Box 29, Folder 1019)
- Reimbursements - Engineering News Record (Selected Articles), 1973-1975 (Box 29, Folder 1020)
- Reimbursements - Environmental / Citizens Groups, 1970-1975 (Box 29, Folder 1021)
- Reimbursements - Environmental Financing Authority (Box 29, Folder 1022)
- Reimbursements - Environmental Impact Statements (EPA Regulations) (Box 29, Folder 1023)
- Reimbursements - EPA Organization and Personnel, 1971-1974 (Box 29, Folder 1024)
- Reimbursements - Federal Facilities (EPA Notice) (Box 29, Folder 1025)
- Reimbursements - Fish Kills, 1969-1972 (Box 29, Folder 1026)
- Reimbursements - Future Commission (National Environmental Assessment Mechanism) Proposed by Dr. Ling, 3-M Corporation, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 1027)
- Reimbursements - 1972-75 Governors (Rosters), 1972-1975 (Box 29, Folder 1028)
- Reimbursements - EPA Grant Awards (Register) Fiscal Year 1972 (Box 30, Folder 1029)
- Reimbursements - EPA Grant Awards - Press Release (Incomplete List) (Box 30, Folder 1030)
- Reimbursements - Great Lakes - International Joint Agreement (IJC) and Lake Erie Legislative Conference, 1973-1976 (Box 30, Folder 1031)
- Reimbursements - International Problems, 1973-1976 (Box 30, Folder 1032)
- Reimbursements - Land Disposal (Muskegon, etc.), 1972-1973 (Box 30, Folder 1033)
- Reimbursements - Marine Sanitation Devices (Boat Pollution), 1971-1975 (Box 30, Folder 1034)
- Reimbursements - National Governors' Conference Committee on Natural Resources and Environmental Management (Box 30, Folder 1035)
- Reimbursements - Ocean Dumping and Sludge Disposal (Legislation and EPA Regulations), 1971-1976 (Box 30, Folder 1036)
- Reimbursements - Oil and Hazardous Substances (EPA Regulations) (Box 30, Folder 1037)
- Reimbursements - Pre-Treatment (by Industry) - EPA Regulations, 1973-1975 (Box 30, Folder 1038)
- Reimbursements - Public Participation (EPA Regulations) (Box 30, Folder 1039)
- Reimbursements - Regional Operating Guidance (EPA) (Box 30, Folder 1040)
- Reimbursements - Regulations (EPA) General and Status, end of 1973 (Box 30, Folder 1041)
- Reimbursements - Secondary Treatment (EPA Regulations) (Box 30, Folder 1042)
- Reimbursements - Sewer Systems Evaluation - EPA Guidelines ("Infiltration/Inflow") (Box 30, Folder 1043)
- Reimbursements - Southern Environmental Resources Conference, Charleston, S.C., May 1973 (Box 30, Folder 1044)
- Reimbursements - Storm Water Runoff and Separate Sewers - EPA Regulations (Box 30, Folder 1045)
- Reimbursements - Tax Amortization (Box 30, Folder 1046)
- Reimbursements - TVA Pollution Control Facilities, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 1047)
- Reimbursements - Test Procedures and Analysis of Pollutants (sec 304 (g) of PL92-500 EPA) (Box 30, Folder 1048)
- Reimbursements - Thermal Pollution, 1971-1974 (Box 30, Folder 1049)
- Reimbursements - Toxic Pollutants - EPA Regulations (Box 30, Folder 1050)
- Reimbursements - Training (Manpower), 1972-1973 (Box 30, Folder 1051)
- Reimbursements - Turnkey - EPA Regulations (Box 30, Folder 1052)
  Construction of waste treatment facilities
- Reimbursements - User Charges and Industrial Cost Recovery (Payback) EPA Regulations (Box 30, Folder 1053)
- Water Pollution Control Federation - General (Box 30, Folder 1054)
- Water Pollution Control Federation - Questionnaire - Water Quality Status, May 1972 (Box 30, Folder 1055)
- Water Pollution Control Federation - Report on Research, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 1056)
- Water Pollution Control Federation - Workshops on PL92-500 (Box 30, Folder 1057)
- Water Pollution Control Federation - Government Affairs Seminar, March 1972 (Box 30, Folder 1058)
- Water Pollution Control Federation - Annual Conference, Atlanta, Georgia, October 1972 (Box 30, Folder 1059)
- Water Pollution Control Federation - Government Affairs Seminar, April 1973 (Box 30, Folder 1060)
- Water Pollution Control Federation - Annual Conference, Cleveland, Ohio, October 1973 (Box 30, Folder 1061)
  See NAR speech folder
- Water Pollution Control Federation - Government Affairs Seminar, March 1974 (Box 30, Folder 1062)
- Water Pollution Control Federation - Annual Conference, Denver, Colorado, October 1974 (Box 30, Folder 1063)
- Water Pollution Control Federation - Government Affairs Seminar, April 1975 (Box 30, Folder 1064)
- Water Pollution Control Federation - Annual Conference, Miami, Florida, October 1975 (Box 30, Folder 1065)
- Water Pollution Control Federation - Government Affairs Seminar - NCWQ Program Staff Presentation, April 1976 (Box 30, Folder 1066)
- Water Pollution Control Federation - Annual Conference, Minneapolis, Minnesota, October 1976 (Box 30, Folder 1067)
- Water Pollution Control Federation - Amendments to Act: Proposed Legislation and Oversight Hearing, 1974-1976 (Box 30, Folder 1068)
- Water Pollution Control Federation - Effluent Guidelines (Overall) (Box 30, Folder 1069)
- Water Pollution Control Federation - Effluent Standards and Water Quality Information Advisory Committee (Sec.515 of PL92-500) ESQUIAC (Box 30, Folder 1070)
- Water Pollution Control Federation - Refuse Act of 1899 and Industrial Pollution, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 1071)
- Water Pollution Control Federation - Enforcement: Reserve Mining Case (Lake Superior), 1970-1976 (Box 30, Folder 1072)
- Water Pollution Control Federation - Enforcement and Suits (Including Those Under 1899 Act), 1971-1972 (Box 30, Folder 1073)
- Water Pollution Control Federation (Box 30, Folder 1074)
- Water Pollution Control Federation - Permits - States' and CEQ Proposed Amendments to Legislation, September-December 1971 (Box 30, Folder 1075)
- Water Pollution Control Federation - Refuse Act of 1899 - Kalur Court Decision, December 1971 (Box 31, Folder 1076)
- Water Pollution Control Federation - Refuse Act of 1899, January-September 1972 (Box 31, Folder 1077)
- Water Pollution Control Federation - Permits - State Recommendations (and Gianelli Interest, 1975) (Box 31, Folder 1078)
- Water Pollution Control Federation - Permits - State Role (Houston Conference with EPA), June 1972 (Box 31, Folder 1079)
  See also - Governors' conference
- Water Pollution Control Federation - Permits - Enforcement Questionnaire, June-September 1972 (Box 31, Folder 1080)
- Water Pollution Control Federation - Permits - Implementation (Regulations and Interim Authority to States), 1972-1975 (Box 31, Folder 1081)
- Water Pollution Control Federation - Permits - Municipal, 1973-1975 (Box 31, Folder 1082)
- Water Pollution Control Federation - Permits - State Issuance Permanent Authority, 1973-1974 (Box 31, Folder 1083)
- Water Pollution Control Federation - Permits - Water Pollution Control Boards, 1971-1973 (Box 31, Folder 1084)
- Water Pollution Control Federation - Permits - Trade Secrets and Acquisition of Information, sec.304 (h)(1) of PL92-500 (Box 31, Folder 1085)
- Water Pollution Control Federation - Permits - Application Forms and Deadline for Applying, 1972-1973 (Box 31, Folder 1086)
- Water Pollution Control Federation - Permits - Agriculture and Silviculture (EPA Regulations), 1972-1973 (Box 31, Folder 1087)
- Water Pollution Control Federation - Permits - Monitoring, 1972-1974 (Box 31, Folder 1088)
- Water Pollution Control Federation - 1971 Planning - Funds Under PL660 (Box 31, Folder 1089)
- Water Pollution Control Federation - 1972 Planning - New York State (April-May) (Box 31, Folder 1090)
- Water Pollution Control Federation - 1972 Planning - Provisions in PL92-500 and Overall (Box 31, Folder 1091)
- Water Pollution Control Federation - 1972 Planning - Sec. 201 (Facilities) EPA Regulations (Box 31, Folder 1092)
- Water Pollution Control Federation - 1972-76 Planning - Sec. 208 (Area-wide Management) EPA Regulations, 1972-1976 (Box 31, Folder 1093)
- Water Pollution Control Federation - 1972-75 Planning - Sec. 308(e) Continuing Planning Process - EPA Regulations, 1972-1975 (Box 31, Folder 1094)
- Water Pollution Control Federation - Programs (State) Funds for Sec. 106 of PL92-500, July 1972 (Box 31, Folder 1095)
- Water Pollution Control Federation - Programs (State), Legislative Language and Funds (Box 31, Folder 1096)
- Water Pollution Control Federation - Programs (State) - EPA Regulations (Box 31, Folder 1097)
- Water Pollution Control Federation - Programs (State) - Funding (Box 31, Folder 1098)
- Water Pollution Control Federation - Water Quality Standards, State (Interstate and Intrastate) EPA Regulations (sec. 303 (A) (1 and 2)) (Box 31, Folder 1099)
- Water Pollution Control Federation - Water Quality Criteria (sec.304(a)(1)) for Setting Effluent Guidelines and Water Quality Standards ("Green" and "Blue" Books) (Box 31, Folder 1100)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Part 1 of 4 (Draft) (Box 31, Folder 1101)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Part 2 of 4 (Draft) (Box 31, Folder 1102)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Part 3 of 4 (Draft) (Box 32, Folder 1103)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Addendum, Part 4 of 4 (Draft) (Box 32, Folder 1104)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Appendix, Part 1 (Draft) (Box 32, Folder 1105)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Appendix, Part 2 (Draft) (Box 32, Folder 1106)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Volume 1 of 3 (Final) (Box 32, Folder 1107)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Volume 2 of 3 (Final) (Box 32, Folder 1108)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Volume 3 of 3 (Final) (Box 32, Folder 1109)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Non-Point Sources, by Midwest Research Institute, November 1975 (Box 32, Folder 1110)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Irrigation Return Flow, by Toups Corporation, September 1975 (Box 32, Folder 1111)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Innovative Technology (Draft) by Water Purification Assoc., July 1975 (Box 32, Folder 1112)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Innovative Technology by Water Purification Assoc., August 1975 (Box 32, Folder 1113)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Water Savings by American Water Works Assoc., July 1975 (Box 33, Folder 1114)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Urban Runoff, by Black, Crow and Eidsness, Draft, July 1975 (Box 33, Folder 1115)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Urban Runoff, by Black, Crow and Eidsness, October 1975 (Box 33, Folder 1116)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Needs/Costs of Meeting Requirements of PL92-500, by American Public Works Association, Draft, December 1974 (Box 33, Folder 1117)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Needs/Costs of Meeting Requirements of PL92-500, by American Public Works Association, August 1975 (Box 33, Folder 1118)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Iron and Steel, by Arthur G. McKee, Draft, March 1975 (Box 33, Folder 1119)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Iron and Steel, by Arthur G. McKee, Supplemental Technology (Box 33, Folder 1120)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Iron and Steel, by Arthur G. McKee, November 1975 (Box 33, Folder 1121)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Chemicals, Organic, by Catalytic, June 1975 (Box 33, Folder 1122)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Chemicals, Inorganic, by Catalytic, July 1975 (Box 34, Folder 1123)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Petroleum Refining, by Engineering Sciences, June 1975 (Box 34, Folder 1124)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Petroleum Refining, Appendix, by Engineering Sciences, June 1975 (Box 34, Folder 1125)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Pulp and Paper, Study by Hazen and Sawyer, Draft, February 1975 (Box 34, Folder 1126)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Pulp and Paper, Study by Hazen and Sawyer, May 1975 (Box 34, Folder 1127)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Electroplating (Metal Finishing), by Lancy Laboratories, Draft, April 1975 (Box 34, Folder 1128)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Electroplating (Metal Finishing), by Lancy Laboratories, October 1975 (Box 34, Folder 1129)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Canned Fruits and Vegetables, by Environmental Associates, June 1975 (Box 34, Folder 1130)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Plastics and Synthetics, by Procon, Inc., Draft, February 1975 (Box 35, Folder 1131)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Plastics and Synthetics, by Procon, Inc., September 1975 (Box 35, Folder 1132)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Textiles, by Lockwood Greene Engineers, Draft, February 1975 (Box 35, Folder 1133)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Textiles, by Lockwood Greene Engineers, June 1975 (Box 35, Folder 1134)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - General Industries, by Battelle Memorial Institute, Vol. I, July 1975 (Box 35, Folder 1135)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Technology, by Battelle Memorial Institute, Vol. II, July 1975 (Box 35, Folder 1136)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Industry Categories, by Battelle Memorial Institute, Vol. III, July 1975 (Box 35, Folder 1137)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Industry Categories, by Battelle Memorial Institute, Vol. IV, July 1975 (Box 35, Folder 1138)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Steam Electric Power, by Teknekron, Draft, April 1975 (Box 35, Folder 1139)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Steam Electric Power, Vol. I, by Teknekron, December 1975 (Box 36, Folder 1140)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Steam Electric Power, Vol. II, by Teknekron, December 1975 (Box 36, Folder 1141)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Steam Electric Power, Vol. III, by Teknekron, December 1975 (Box 36, Folder 1142)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Steam Electric Power, Draft Appendix to Interim Report, Teknekron, April 1975 (Box 36, Folder 1143)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Eight Case Studies, by Abt Associates, Draft (1 of 3), June 1975 (Box 36, Folder 1144)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Eight Case Studies, by Abt Associates, Draft (2 of 3), June 1975 (Box 36, Folder 1145)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Eight Case Studies, by Abt Associates, Draft (3 of 3), June 1975 (Box 36, Folder 1146)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Eight Case Studies, by Abt Associates, June 1975 (Box 36, Folder 1147)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Chemical Processing Industries, by International Research and Technology Corporation, Draft, August 1975 (Box 36, Folder 1148)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Chemical Processing Industries, by International Research and Technology Corporation, March 1976 (Box 36, Folder 1149)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Costs of Compliance with PL92-500, Group A Industries (Vol. I), by National Planning Association, August 1975 (Box 36, Folder 1150)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Costs of Compliance with PL92-500, Group B and C Industries (Vol. II), by National Planning Association, November 1975 (Box 36, Folder 1151)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Pilot Studies, Five Industries, Draft (Summaries), by the Conference Board (Box 36, Folder 1152)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Pilot Studies, Five Industries, Blast Furnaces and Steel, by the Conference Board (1 of 5), May 1975 (Box 36, Folder 1153)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Pilot Studies, Five Industries, Petroleum Refining, by the Conference Board (2 of 5), July 1975 (Box 37, Folder 1154)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Pilot Studies, Five Industries, Paper, by the Conference Board (3 of 5), June 1975 (Box 37, Folder 1155)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Pilot Studies, Five Industries, Alkalies and Chlorine, by the Conference Board (4 of 5), June 1975 (Box 37, Folder 1156)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Pilot Studies, Five Industries, Industrial Organic Chemicals, by the Conference Board (5 of 5), February 1975 (Box 37, Folder 1157)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - A Methodological Approach to Evaluating the Economic Impact on Industry of Environmental Controls, National Bureau of Economic Research, January 1975 (Box 37, Folder 1158)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Economic Impact of 1972 Amendments to the Water Pollution Control Act on 6 Designated Industries (Executive Summaries) by the National Bureau of Economic Research, January 1975 (Box 37, Folder 1159)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Economic Impact of the Federal Water Pollution Control Acts of 1972 on the Textile Industry, by the National Board of Economic Research, July 1975 (Box 37, Folder 1160)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Economic Impact of the Federal Water Pollution Control Act Amendments of 1972 on the Metal Finishing Industry, June 1975 (Box 37, Folder 1161)
- Publicly Owned Treatment Works - Economic Impact of the Federal Water Pollution Control Act Amendments of 1972 on the Petroleum Refining Industry, by the National Bureau of Economic Research, June 1975 (Box 37, Folder 1162)